Natdanai Thannin

Tel: +66-63-516-4850

Email: natdanaitnn@gmail.com
Alternate email: 678familyz@gmail.com
Portfolio Site: https://natdanai.vercel.app/

Skills: C++, C# .NET, PHP, JavaScript, Lua, Java, Python, React, Next.js, Svelte.

A junior developer with 2 years of experience in frontend and backend developments who is passionate about working in any challenge opportunities. I spend every single day with coding and learning new programming languages and new technologies. I'm not afraid of any problems but I push my effort to solve them for being pleased with success and growing up with failure.

Experiences

FIVEM FREELANCE (2021- present)

Developer

- Developed game play by Lua and Javascript (typescript).
- Implemented user interface with Svelte, React and Next.js.
- Designed the database table on MYSQL.
- Developed in-game music from YouTube for player by using google API.
- Developed server monitoring and notification via Discord by using Discord Api.
- Developed event driven system in backend for communicating between client and server.
- Developed cheating protection by XOR encryption.
- Developed authentication system by using UUID for user identity.
- Developed FiveM website and backend api by using next.js.
- Developed usage transaction and historical enquiry system.
- Developed time synchronization between website and server.
- Developed game top up system.

Orimsa Contact (6 Month)

Developer

- Enchanted application mail server using PHP, Jquery
- Developed application post ads using Vue
- Enchanted website car rental using PHP, Jquery

Icon Framework (2020 - 2021)

Intern Developer

- Developed and maintained e-Property system by using C# and ASP.NET connecting to MSSQL.
- Enhanced the system to collect information of maintenance fee's payment transaction and key card transaction.
- Developed an internal system for inhouse project contained multi-functions such as ticket tracking, project's cost calculation, project member maintenance and time management by using React.js, Nest.js and MSSQL.

Education

Bachelor's Degree of Information Technology | 2017 - 2021

King Mongkut's University of Technology North Bangkok

Senior Project: Medical System for PrachinBuri Provincial Public Health Office | 2021

Programming Language: PHP

- Developed an application for stock checking, herbal disbursing, and medical disbursement.
- Developed administrator system for maintaining and monitoring.
- Developed partner's order tracking and notification system for medical expiration and order alert for making new purchase order to partner.
- Developed reports enquiry system for disbursing, importing, stock remaining and best seller.